stunnish.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy

### Stunnish Entertainment LLC Privacy Policy

This privacy statement covers the entertainment website, Stunnish.com.  Please read this statement in its entirety.  If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us immediately.

### Ownership of Information

Stunnish Entertainment LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on the entertainment website, Stunnish.com.

### **Comments**

In order to enhance the viewers experience, they can choose to leave comments on the articles of their choice.  Stunnish Entertainment LLC does not endorse any comments, as they are opinions of the person commenting and have no association with Stunnish Entertainment or its employees.

### **Mailing List**

Stunnish Entertainment LLC may launch a mailing list for the website Stunnish.com.  In order to sign up to receive regular e-mails from a websites mailing list, users must submit information including: valid e-mail address, location, and interests.  This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general interest in various internal and third party products and services.  All personal information will not be shared with any other organization.  Users who choose to sign up for the mailing list will receive regular e-mails from Stunnish.com, which include new articles, as well as emails from third party sponsors.  If you do not want to receive e-mails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

### Third Party Cookies

Business partners may use cookies on our website (example: advertisers).  However, Stunnish Entertainment LLC has no access to or control over these cookies.  This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Stunnish Entertainment LLC only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### **Third Party Advertising**

The advertisements appearing on Stunnish Entertainment LLC websites are presented to the user by third party advertisers including Google, among others.  These companies may use information (Not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to Stunnish.com in order to provide advertisements on this website and other websites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  This website allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you and other internet users visit.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (example: browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These companies typically use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

### ****Log Files

Like most standard website servers we use log files.  This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the website, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.  We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

### Legal Disclaimer

We make every effort possible to preserve user privacy on our websites, however, Stunnish Entertainment LLC may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website, Stunnish.com

### **Business Transitions**

In the event Stunnish Entertainment LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

### **Links**

The Stunnish Entertainment LLC website, Stunnish.com, contains links to other websites.  Please be aware that Stunnish Entertainment LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.  This privacy statement applies to information collected by Stunnish Entertainment LLC.

### Notification of Changes

Whenever Stunnish Entertainment LLC changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.

### **Copyright Information**

All images on Stunnish.com are readily available in various places on the internet and believed to be in public domain.  Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the U.S. Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.).  If you believe that any content appearing on Stunnish.com infringes on your copyright, please let us know immediately.  E-mail stunnishmedia[at]gmail[dot]com following information to us and the infringing material will be removed as soon as possible.

A.  Your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;

B.  A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;

C.  The exact URL or a description of each place were alleged infringing material is located;

D.  A Statement by you that you have good faith belief that the disputed use has not been authorized to act on your behalf; and

E.  Your electronic or physical signature or the electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf; and

F.  A statement by you made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.

Please also note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.
